Yair Charit

+972-54-440-8838 yaircharit@gmail.com 🙎 linkedin.com/in/yair-charit in yaircharit.github.io

Summary:

B.Sc. in Computer Science Graduate from Tel-Hai College, Israel. Great working as part of a team as well as leading it when necessary. Experienced working and communicating online. Working knowledge in continuous integration development process.

Experience:

2021 - present: Software Quality Assurance at Biosense Webster, Yokneam. Working on the core product of Biosense Webster- CARTO 3. The CARTO 3 System is an advanced 3D mapping system with integration. scalability, and insights, supporting electrophysiologists in making optimal treatment decisions.

2020 - present: freelancer full stack web developer: custom automations, dynamic pages, database set-up and interface, etc.

2019 - present: Assembly and OS Instructor at "Magshimim", Cyber Education Center. Teaching and managing a class, delivering complex ideas in limited time (currently online)

Skills:

Software Development • Full-Stack Development • Software Quality Assurance • Problem Solving • Bash • C • C++ • C# • Java • Python • SQL • .NET • MATLAB • Git BASH • Assembly

Education:



2018 – 2021: (B.Sc.) Computer Science - Tel-Hai college, Israel.

- Outstanding performance in all programming focus courses.
- Deep understanding of OOP coding and computer's fundamentals (low and high level programming languages).



2012–2016: Highschool education- "Hamoshava", Zichron Ya'aqov.

- 5 units in Computer Science and English
- Excelled in Computer Science.

Qualifications:



2018: English for Work – The Language Gallery, London

Languages:

Fluent in Hebrew and English.